rimmkaufman.com 2013-04-13

# Privacy Policy | Data-Driven Online Marketing | RKG

### Our sites

Our two public websites are [http://www.rimmkaufman.com](http://www.rimmkaufman.com/), and [http://www.rkdms.com](http://www.rkdms.com/).

We use the [rimmkaufman.com](http://www.rimmkaufman.com/) site to describe our company. We use the rkdms.com site to help our clients count visitors coming to their websites from different sources.

### Contact us

Contact us if you have questions about this policy. You can e-mail us at [info@rimmkaufman.com](mailto:info@rimmkaufman.com), or you can call us at 434-970-1010. Our mailing address is: Rimm-Kaufman Group LLC, Box 8025, Charlottesville, Virginia 22906, USA.

### Disputes

If you think we’ve not followed our privacy policy in some way, please contact us.

### Data collection

We collect two different types of data: non-identifiable basic information and non-identifiable cookies.

### We collect non-identifiable basic information

We collect click-stream data, HTTP protocol elements, and search terms. We use these data for research and development, system tracking, and helping visitors reach the right page. We use these data ourselves, and we share aggregated data with our clients. These data are non-identifiable. This means we can’t (and have no interest in trying to) identify any individual person via these data. We also collect access logs and search strings. We use these data to help improve our site and our clients’ sites.

### We collect non-identifiable cookie information

We collect HTTP cookie data. Again, we use these data for research and development, system tracking, and helping visitors reach the right page. We use these data ourselves and we share aggregated data with our clients. Our cookies are non-identifiable, meaning we can’t (and don’t want to) identify you or any individual person via these data. We collect these cookie data to help improve our web site and our clients’ web sites.

### What are “cookies”?

A cookie is a piece of information sent to a browser by a web server. The browser then returns that information to the Web server. This is how some Web pages “remember” your previous visits; for example, an e-commerce site might use a cookie to remember which items you’ve placed in your online shopping cart. Cookies can also store user preference information, log-in data, etc. Cookies let sites provide you with tailored information.

### Links to other sites

Our sites link to and redirect to third-party websites. We’re not responsible for the privacy practices or the content on those sites.

When you leave our site, it is wise to check the privacy policy of the site you reach. Those sites might place their own cookies, collect data, and use personal information in different ways than we do.

The privacy policy described on this page only applies to our sites.

### Security

We have security measures in place to protect the information we collect. We use strong encryption to keep these data safe from loss, tampering, misuse, and unathorized access.

### Policy changes

Should we modify our privacy policy, we’ll update this page accordingly.If we make changes to our policy, we’ll treat previously collected data in accordance with our policy in effect when the data were collected.

### Individuals under 13 years of age

We’re strongly committed to protecting the on-line privacy of kids. In accordance with the Children’s On-line Privacy Protection Act, we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Our firm does not market to children, nor do we provide any services to children.

### P3P: Platform for Privacy Preferences

Our privacy policy is available in machine readable format for browsers supporting P3P in [XML](http://www.rimmkaufman.com/w3c/policy1.xml) and [compact form](http://www.rimmkaufman.com/privacy-policy/compact-privacy-policy/).

For more info, visit <http://www.w3.org/TR/p3pdeployment>.

### Acceptance of this privacy policy

By using this site, you’re indicating you’ve read and accept our privacy policy. If you don’t agree with this policy, please do not use our site. Continuing to use of this site after we post changes to these terms means you accept those changes.Thanks.
